bnu.com.mo 2013-05-24

# BNU – Macau » BNU Privacy Policy

### BNU Privacy Policy

BNU’s privacy policy applies to both “online” and offline transactions, being also available for consultation at all BNU Branch network.

Your personal information is important to us and Banco Nacional Ultramarino S.A. (the “Bank”) will protect your privacy to the fullest extent possible, regardless of whether you are one of our clients.

Except with your authorization or as may be required by law, we will not disclose, share, sell or divulge any of your personal information to other parties. We protect your personal information as well as your business activities and transactions, in accordance with our internal security policies and applicable laws.

Personal data or financial information you make available to or may be requested by the Bank will be used to enable us to provide services to you, conduct credit checks, ensure client’s continuing credit worthiness, evaluate credit applications, meet disclosure or other requirements imposed by law or ordered by a lawful authority, collect debts or designing financial products or services. The Bank maintains appropriate measures to ensure that all personal data is securely stored as long as it is necessary for us to provide services to you or to comply with retention obligations imposed by law, after which it will be destroyed. All of our staff and third parties with permitted access to your information are specifically required to observe the Bank’s confidentiality obligations. We strive to ensure that your personal data is protected against accidental or unauthorized access, processing or deletion.

Your personal data may also be used by the Bank or transmitted to other parties, for the purposes of marketing products or services which we believe you may be interested in. You are entitled to opt-out from receiving our marketing or promotional materials, if you so wish.

The Bank may from time to time request your personal data, in order to provide services you have applied for or to ensure that the Bank’s records are correct and up to date. If you choose not to provide requested data or if information provided is incomplete or incorrect, this may prevent the Bank from providing services to you.

The Bank may be ordered to provide users’ personal data or financial information to government departments responsible for banking supervision or to Macau SAR courts, but we will only do so under proper authority.

By opening an account or requesting services from us, or by accessing this website and/or using the BNU On-line services you acknowledge, accept and authorize the Bank to collect and/or transfer your personal data and/or information related to transactions you undertake with the Bank to other parties, insofar as such collection or transmission is necessary for the Bank to provide services to you as you may request, to enable the Bank to comply with reporting obligations, for the Bank’s internal or external auditing purposes, and to the extent that such transfer is required to comply with reporting obligations and consolidation of accounts within the CGD Group in Portugal.

Any such transmission shall be undertaken in strict compliance with applicable banking secrecy and personal data privacy laws.

The secure areas of this website use digital encryption technologies, to ensure that sensitive data, such as payment or transfer instructions are kept confidential. Because the security and confidentiality of ordinary e-mail cannot be guaranteed, we will not send personal or financially sensitive information by unencrypted e-mail, unless you expressly instruct us otherwise.

Any individual has the right to inquire if the Bank holds personal data about them, and to have access to such data. Also, individuals are entitled that such data be corrected, if found inaccurate. The Bank is entitled to charge a reasonable fee for processing data access requests.

Any requests or enquiries related to personal data may be directed to

the Compliance Office

(to the attention of the Compliance Officer)

Banco Nacional Ultramarino, S.A.  
Avenida de Almeida Ribeiro, 22  
Macau
